{
    "id": "12930035ca4d45e8876ea0453ee2ddfe",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The people ............................... walked in just now seem to be rich.",
            "description": "We use who to refer to people.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The girl ...................................... answered the phone seemed rather clueless.",
            "description": "When the relative pronoun is the subject of the relative clause, we use who to refer to people. ",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is the person ........................................ called the police?",
            "description": "When the relative pronoun is the subject of the relative clause, we use who to refer to people.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have lost the paper on ...................................... I had written her address.",
            "description": "In relative clauses which is used to refer to inanimate objects. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is the woman ...................................... I have always wanted to marry.",
            "description": "Here the relative pronoun is the object of the relative clause hence we use whom. ",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The woman .................................... child had gone missing was frantic.",
            "description": "In relative clauses whose replaces words like her or his.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "who's",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I know a girl ........................................ father is an artist.",
            "description": "In relative clauses whose replaces words like her or his.",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "whose",
                "who's"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The man .................................... bag was stolen complained to the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whose",
                "who's"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is that girl ..................................... is sitting beside James?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "who's",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I talked to a man ......................................... had just returned from an overseas trip.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ....................................... has nothing to lose has no worries.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The woman ....................................... you can see over there is my cousin.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}